reshish.com 2019-07-18

# Privacy Policy

We do not collect or store any personally identifiable information.  
If you enter your email in the feedback form (which is not required) it may be used for a reply only and is not stored.

We may use cookies to store matrices for the “Restore matrix” functionality only if HTML5 Local Storage is unavailable. We also use cookies for security purposes of the site. Nevertheless, it is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

We use advertising companies such as Ezoic, Google Adsense and Sovrn to serve ads on our website. They may use cookies to collect data to show you personalized ads based on your interests.

Ezoic handles privacy consent settings on our site supported by its [service Privacy Policy](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/reshish.com).

We use web analytics services such as Google Analytics and Yandex Metrica for tracking the number of visits, their interaction with the site and other related data. We use that information to examine our site performance.

Information collected by these tools is used in accordance with their own privacy polices that can be found on their websites. Our site doesn’t control cookies used by third parties advertisers and services.

Our site may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for privacy practices of those sites.

We may update this Privacy Policy at any time in the future.

By using our website you consent to this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy you can contact us by email at reshish@yahoo.com or using the [feedback form](http://reshish.com/feedback.php).

Last updated: 05/18/2018
